# Chris Tsoukaladelis

https://tsoukaladelis.xyz chris@lainwired.net

## About Me

I'm currently a PhD candidate at Stony Brook University, where I work with Prof. Nick Nikiforakis in the PragSec lab. My main areas of interest is web integrity and transparency, and orthogonally I do research on system isolation-based security and web application debloating. I am passionate about privacy, anonymity and freedom on the web.

#### **Publications**

- The Times, They Are A-Changin': Characterizing Post-Publication Changes to Online News
  - IEEE Symposium on Security and Privacy 2024 (IEEE S&P '24)
- Manufactured Narratives: On the Potential of Manipulating Social Media to Politicize World Events
  - IEEE Symposium on Security and Privacy Workshops 2024 (IEEE S&PW '24)
- AnimateDead: Debloating Web Applications Using Concolic Execution Usenix Security 2023 (USENIX '23)

## Education

**Stony Brook University** 

2021 - Present

PhD Candidate

**University of Patras** 

2014 - 2020

Engineer's Degree (BS+MS equivalent) in electrical and computer engineering

## Experience

## **Stony Brook University**

2021 - Present

Research Assistant

PragSec lab: My main focus is on web content integrity and transparency. Orthogonally, I have worked on web application debloating and other areas of web security.

## **University of Patras**

2017 - 2020

Research Assistant

 Computer Systems lab: I worked on developing and maintaining a malware detection and classification platform.
I also participated in various online capture the flag (CtF) competitions.

## **Datawise Data Engineering LLC**

2018 - 2020

DevOps, Security Consultant

 Security Consultant: I was a consultant for various security decisions made in the handling of sensitive data

## **Awards**

- SecWeb 2024 Best Paper Award
- CSAW 2024 Applied Research Competition 2nd Place

## Skills

- o Programming Python, C/C++, Go, PHP, Javascript, Bash, x86 ASM
- System administration Linux, openBSD
- Web application debloating, sandboxing
- o Browser automation
- Bot automation & analysis of anti-bot mechanisms